[
	{
		"question": "What can TACC users use MATLAB for?",
		"desired answer": "only for non-commercial, academic purposes"
	},

	{
		"question": "How do I load MATLAB?",
		"desired answer": "module load matlab"
	},

	{
		"question": "Should I launch MATLAB jobs on login nodes?",
		"desired answer": "Do NOT launch MATLAB on the login nodes"
	},

	{
		"question": "Where can I submit my MATLAB jobs?",
		"desired answer": "on the TACC resources, e.g. Frontera, Stampede3, or Lonestar6"
	},

	{
		"question": "Why can I not use MATLAB on login nodes?",
		"desired answer": "This may fail and, more importantly, it will prevent other users from doing their work, as your execution will take up too many cycles on the shared login node"
        },

	{
		"question": "How do I invoke MATLAB?",
		"desired answer": "matlab"
	},

	{
		"question": "What is the command to invoke MATLAB?",
		"desired answer": "matlab"
	},

	{
		"question": "What is the standard way to submit a Slurm job?",
		"desired answer": "sbatch myjobscript"
	},

	{
		"question": "How do I submit a Slurm job?",
		"desired answer": "sbatch myjobscript"
	},

	{
		"question": "How is using login nodes for MATLAB jobs system abuse?",
		"desired answer": "it will prevent other users from doing their work, as your execution will take up too many cycles on the shared login node"
	}
]
